(Penny:)Oh, my gosh. I can't believe it.
Really?
(Penny:)Oh, I'm so excited. Thank you.
(Penny:)Thank you so much. Okay, bye.
I got the hemorrhoid commercial.
I start Monday.
(Sheldon:)What about Nebraska?
(Penny:)Oh, hell with Nebraska.
I'm gonna be a star.
(Sheldon(to Leonard):)Have you ever thought
of teaching physics?
(Actress:)Ready to ride?
(Penny(on screen):)I don't think so, Mom.
(Penny(on screen):)Not today.
(Actress:)Oh, sweetie.
Hemorrhoids acting up again?
You don't know the haIf of it.
(Actress:)Oh, yes, I do.
(Actress:)Try a dab of this.
"Rose-scented Preparation-H
for women?"
(Actress:)Now, the H is for her.
- I'm proud of you.
- Shh. Here comes my joke.
How you doing?
Sitting pretty.